[{"answer": "That does go along with the fact that I'm hearing that Ariel Castro had a hierarchy.", "docId": "130514pmt", "aSentId": 36, "question": "From what you've been hearing, Ed, from your sources, consistent with everything that is now building up about the reality of the horror that went on in that house?", "qSentId": 35}, {"answer": "That's right.", "docId": "130514pmt", "aSentId": 44, "question": "Is that right?", "qSentId": 43}, {"answer": "Well, I'm hearing from the interrogation that he really didn't deny anything, but he didn't admit it.", "docId": "130514pmt", "aSentId": 54, "question": "What do you make of that?", "qSentId": 53}, {"answer": "Well, it is.", "docId": "130514pmt", "aSentId": 60, "question": "I mean, this is a defense that's going to be extremely difficult to sustain itself, isn't it?", "qSentId": 59}, {"answer": "I was shocked.", "docId": "130514pmt", "aSentId": 71, "question": "What was your reaction, when you first heard that Ariel Castro, the father of the man that you were married to, had been arrested in connection with this awful crime, series of crimes, what was your reaction?", "qSentId": 70}, {"answer": "I never had the desire to get to know him personally or very closely.", "docId": "130514pmt", "aSentId": 76, "question": "What kind of man -- what kind of man was he?", "qSentId": 75}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130514pmt", "aSentId": 93, "question": "And he also beat your ex-husband repeatedly when he was younger, is that right?", "qSentId": 92}, {"answer": "It's much like everyone else describes.", "docId": "130514pmt", "aSentId": 101, "question": "What was the experience of being in that house with Ariel Castro like?", "qSentId": 100}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "130514pmt", "aSentId": 116, "question": "Have you talked to your ex-husband since the revelations of a week ago?", "qSentId": 115}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130514pmt", "aSentId": 121, "question": "Did you believe them when you saw their interview?", "qSentId": 120}, {"answer": "Oh, well, definitely, but I mean, I wish they had, but I can see how perhaps not.", "docId": "130514pmt", "aSentId": 147, "question": "Do you think the scale of what he was doing even then warranted more attention?", "qSentId": 146}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "130514pmt", "aSentId": 157, "question": "Did you know her?", "qSentId": 156}, {"answer": "I don't believe so, or if I did, it wasn't in any, you know, lasting capacity.", "docId": "130514pmt", "aSentId": 161, "question": "But you never encountered her?", "qSentId": 160}, {"answer": "Just anguish.", "docId": "130514pmt", "aSentId": 170, "question": "What is your overriding reaction?", "qSentId": 169}, {"answer": "That's certainly one way to put it.", "docId": "130514pmt", "aSentId": 203, "question": "Dana, this is a right old mess for the president, isn't it?", "qSentId": 202}, {"answer": "That's absolutely right.", "docId": "130514pmt", "aSentId": 239, "question": "Now, where and how is that line drawn, and how far over it from this report do we think they crossed?", "qSentId": 238}, {"answer": "Well, maybe B-plus but I'm mystified by the legalistic language.", "docId": "130514pmt", "aSentId": 256, "question": "Has the White House handled this properly, do you think?", "qSentId": 255}, {"answer": "Sure.", "docId": "130514pmt", "aSentId": 265, "question": "Is it really feasible, do you think, that the IRS would independently be so overtly political against the Republicans and Tea Party in particular without anybody at the White House having at least had a quiet word?", "qSentId": 264}, {"answer": "First of all, I think it's a crime.", "docId": "130514pmt", "aSentId": 289, "question": "Should there be proof that emerges that somebody at the White House knew that the IRS were targeting the Tea Party and so on, how serious would that be?", "qSentId": 288}, {"answer": "Well, full disclosure, I'm not only a friend but a great admirer of Eric Holder's for many, many years.", "docId": "130514pmt", "aSentId": 303, "question": "Does that in itself justify what they did in terms of basically going after the Associated Press and potentially checking the records of up to 100 journalists?", "qSentId": 302}, {"answer": "Well, there is a ground for subpoenaing documents.", "docId": "130514pmt", "aSentId": 313, "question": "And I suppose it really comes down to was what they did actually legal?", "qSentId": 312}, {"answer": "Well, they certainly did remove those references, whether they were removed by the CIA or whether they were removed by people in the State Department is unclear.", "docId": "130514pmt", "aSentId": 334, "question": "And I think they have a right to do that, don't they?", "qSentId": 333}, {"answer": "I agree with you.", "docId": "130514pmt", "aSentId": 344, "question": "Why not communicate that right up front?", "qSentId": 343}, {"answer": "So look, yes, there's a breach of trust because of the opaqueness of the way the White House has handled it, at least starting with the talking points.", "docId": "130514pmt", "aSentId": 347, "question": "I think you put it all together with the IRS targeting the Tea Party, the Benghazi issue of these talking points and al Qaeda references being removed, the A.P. being targeted by the Justice Department, in what many consider to be an outrageous manner -- you put it all together, and you have a real breach of trust in President Obama and his administration, don't you?", "qSentId": 346}, {"answer": "It can.", "docId": "130514pmt", "aSentId": 422, "question": "That eliminates a lot of people, doesn't it?", "qSentId": 421}, {"answer": "It is.", "docId": "130514pmt", "aSentId": 451, "question": "Is that one of the wonders of modern science, if you like?", "qSentId": 450}, {"answer": "I think she did tremendous goodwill and good work on behalf of women worldwide.", "docId": "130514pmt", "aSentId": 467, "question": "Just one last question, Dr. Sussman: do you believe, from your medical perspective, that this simple op-ed piece and the worldwide reaction can save a lot of lives?", "qSentId": 466}]